{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_Lakes",
    "predicate": "property/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/The_Queen's_College,_Oxford",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Lakes attended The Queen's College, Oxford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9641799926757812,
            "question": "Was Arthur Lakes a student at The Queen's College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219738841056824,
            "question": "Where did Arthur Lakes attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9113995432853699,
            "question": "Did Arthur Lakes study at a college in England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819438219070435,
            "question": "What is the name of the college that Arthur Lakes attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8782527446746826,
            "question": "Which university did Arthur Lakes attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8725298047065735,
            "question": "In what city did Arthur Lakes attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8328957557678223,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution that Arthur Lakes attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7870129346847534,
            "question": "Is The Queen's College located in Oxford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46634015440940857,
            "question": "What is the location of The Queen's College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4170862138271332,
            "question": "What type of institution is The Queen's College?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Lakes attended The Queen's College, Oxford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2767_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the location of The Queen's College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2767_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Queen's College located in Oxford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2767_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the institution that Arthur Lakes attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2767_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2767_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you want to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information and the query, I get:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe reason is that the documents mention Arthur Lakes attending \"Queen Elizabeth College Guernsey\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2767/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt) and \"Queens College, Oxford, until 1865\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2767/re-ranker-msmarco/28.txt), but they do not mention The Queen's College, Oxford."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Arthur Lakes was educated at Queens College, Oxford. This supports the statement that Arthur Lakes attended The Queen's College, Oxford."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Context information 3 contradicts it.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}